雷蒙德
Raymond!
雷 亲爱的
Ray? Sweetie?
我弹得很响
I play it loud.
就不会听到他的声音
Like, I can't hear him.
收拾好你的东西 你要回医院
Pack your things, you're going back to the hospital.
我要打电话给你爸 让他把你带去
I'm calling daddy and he is taking you back.
不要
No.
恶魔的糖果
译者：微博@Emtee
妈妈说你必须快点了
Mom said you have to hurry.
嘿
Hey.
那是给银行的东西吗
Is that the thing for the bank?
是啊 没错 我接的活
Yeah. Yeah, that's a commission.
蝴蝶? 无关金属啊
Butterflies? So not metal.
我知道 我知道 我同意
I know, I know, I agree.
但多数人不喜欢金属
But most people don't like metal.
多数人喜欢的是...
Most people's taste is in their..
你还没洗澡吗 我们要迟到了
Have you not showered yet? We're late.
伙计们 我们能听
Guys, can we listen to something
稍微不这么重的吗
just a little bit less heavy?
金属乐队?
Metallica?
我可不确定你妈想听这个
I'm not sure that's what your mom had in mind.
真漂亮
It's gorgeous.
我这辈子都住在德克萨斯
Lived in Texas my whole life.
天气一直很热
It's always been hot
热得连撒旦都会祈求下雨
but well, even Satan's praying for it to rain.
你们能看到这里的一切都有着
As y'all can see, everything's true
世纪之交时的真实样貌
to the turn of the century period.
没错 我喜欢这墙纸
Yeah, I love this wallpaper.
- 很特别 对吧 - 没错
Special, ain't it? - Yeah.
走过这边 朝北的方向 有双悬窗
And through here, north facin', double hung windows.
有阳光照射进来
Sunlight streamin' in.
让人感觉恬静 我不擅长华丽的辞藻 但脑海中浮现的就是这个词
I'm not one for flowery words, but tranquil comes to mind.
小佐 这房间比你现在住的
Zo, this is twice the size of the room
大两倍
that you have right now.
开心点 你把你的海报
Have fun, you're not gonna see any of them
都贴满就看不到了
with all the posters that you have.
哪怕有一只泰迪贴不掉
If there's even one teddy left..
你也得再给我买些
...you have to buy me some more.
- 好吗 - 行 没问题
Okay? - Yeah. Of course.
将来等孩子准备好
Could make a mighty fine bedroom
要些私人空间时
for a teenager down the track.
就能给她做一间非常棒的卧室
When she's ready for some space of her own.τгаηslаτed ьγ ωeiьо-Eмτee
这里会是爸爸的工作室
This is gonna be daddy's studio.
或一间工作室 没错
Or a studio. Yes, indeed.
好了
Okay.
根据法律 我必须说明这栋房子里死过人
By law I have to fess up to any death in the house.
死过两个人
And in this case there were two.
亲爱的
Um, sweetie.
我把包落车上了
I had left my bag in the car
包里有我需要的文件
and it's got some documents I need.
你要我离开就直说
If you want me to leave, just ask.
好的
Okay.
你卖不掉
And now you can't sell it
所以价格才这么低
which is why the price is so low.
下一批看房的11点到
Next showings at eleven..
一天的时间我都排满了
...got 'em lined up all day.
人人都爱便宜货
Folks love a bargain.
总之 事情是这样的
After all, what are we talkin' about here?
一位亲爱的小老太不小心
A sweet little old lady who accidentally
从楼梯摔落 她亲爱的丈夫
fell down the stairs, and her dear old hubby
受不了没有她的生活
who couldn't stand to live without her.
确实让人难过
Sad, indeed..
但不是那种杀人魔查理·曼森住的地方
...but it's not like Charlie Manson lived here.
请让我们单独谈谈 好吗
Can you give us a minute, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你不觉得瘆人吗 - 什么
You don't find it creepy? - What?
- 那对夫妇? - 是啊
The couple? - Yeah.
不觉得 我倒觉得挺浪漫
No. No, I actually think it's really romantic.
他爱她爱得受不了没有她的日子
He loved her so much he couldn't live another day without her.
你只是想要这个工作室
You just want this studio.
什么 没有 我都没在想这事
What? No. I'm not even thinkin' about this.
- 你能听到吗 - 什么 什么
Can you hear that? - What? What?
- 等等 嘘  - 什么意思 什么啊
Wait, shh. - What do you mean, what?
就这个声音
That right there.
阿斯特丽德
Astrid..
杰希
Jesse..
- 你听不到吗 - 听不到
You can't hear that? - No, I can't hear that.
- 什么啊 - 买下我
What is it? - Buy me.
你听不到吗 在对我大喊呢
You don't hear that? 'Cause it's screaming at me.
我没法置之不理
I can't ignore it.
我能帮你什么忙吗
Can I help you?
佐伊得换学校
Zooey's gonna have to change schools.
她没问题的 她是个勇敢的孩子
She'll be alright, she's a brave kid.
我要坐两辆公车才能到美容院
It's like two buses for me to get to the salon.
我们再买一辆车就不用了
Not if we get a second car.
你得接更多的活
You have to do more commissions.
光靠我一个人的薪水可办不到
We just, we cannot do this on my salary alone.
我意思是 房租是一回事
I mean rent is one thing
但我们可是按揭付款
but this...this is a serious mortgage.
我知道 阿斯特丽德
I know, Astrid,
给银行画该死的蝴蝶让我想吐
why do you think I'm painting fuckin' butterflies
但我还是画了 你觉得是为了什么
for a bank even though it makes me want to puke?
阿斯特丽德 放松下吧
Astrid, please, chill.
好了
Alright.
就抽一口
Please just, just take a hit.
好吗
Okay?
吐气
Exhale.
很好
Good.
闭上双眼
Close your eyes.
跟着我说
Repeat after me..
我们刚买了一栋房子
We just bought a house.
- 我们刚买了一栋房子 - 没错
"We just bought a house." - Yeah!
是一栋漂亮得不得了的房子
And it's a beautiful fuckin' house.
- 是一栋漂亮得不得了的房子 - 没错
"And it is a beautiful fucking house." - Yeah.
我们会幸福的
We're gonna be happy.
"We're going to be happy."
因为我们再也不用看那种景观
'Cause we never have to look at that view ever again.
来
Come here.
郡警长办公室的 开门
County Sheriff's office, open up.
你能把门开大点让我看清楚吗
Can you open up a little so I can see?
你知道我为什么来吗
You know why I'm here?
有人举报音乐太吵
I got a call about some loud music.
你叫什么
What's your name?
雷
Ray.
你会行个方便保持安静吧 雷
You gonna help us both out and keep quiet, Ray?
会
Yeah.
说出来
Let me hear you say it.
我会行个方便保持安静
I'm gonna help us both out and keep quiet.
很好 但愿我不用再来
Good. I don't want to have to come back.
我再来的话 我就没办法了
If I come back, I got no choice
只能给你一张传票或是罚单
but to give you a citation or ticket
或者更糟 把你逮捕
or worse, place you under arrest.
我可不想这样
I'd much rather not.
永远不会像你想的那么糟
It's never as bad as you think.
说真的 你只要熬过前30分钟
Seriously, you just tough out the first 30 minutes
之后就好了
and then the rest is gravy.
我讨厌这样
I hate gravy.
好了 走吧 勇士
Alright, go forth brave soldier.
不要让学校妨碍了你自身的教育 好吗
Don't let your schooling get in the way of your education, alright?
好的 我爱你 爸爸
Uh, yeah. I love you, dad.
嘿 小佐
Hey, Zo.
天呐
My God.
佐伊
Zooey.
我很久没把你吓成这样了
I haven't gotten you that good in ages.
是啊 太疯狂了
Yeah, that was, that was hysterical.
- 超有意思  - 谢谢
That was super funny. - Thank you.
你的第一天怎么样
How was your first day?
糟透了
Sucked big time.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
会好起来的 我保证
It'll get better, I promise.
好吗 这只是时间问题
Okay? It just takes time.
新事物都需要时间来适应
Yeah, anything new, it just takes time.
蝴蝶呢
What happened to the butterflies?
杰希 杰希
Jess? Jess?
杰希
Jesse!
你神游到哪去了
Wh...where were you?
什么
What?
你神游到哪去了
Where were you?
我去开
I'll get it!
你好
Hi.
来了个人 但不是送披萨的
There's someone here and it's not the pizza man.
你好
Hi.
我有一把这样的
I've got one just like that.
飞行五号
A flying V.
你有一把红色的飞行五号?
You got a red Flying V?
我想要一把吉布森飞行五号
I want a Gibson Flying V
就是金属乐队的柯克·哈米特用的那把
like Kirk Hammett from Metallica uses.
他是我最喜欢的吉他英雄
He is my favorite guitar hero.
我叫我爸妈给我买一把当生日礼物
I mean I asked mom and dad to get one for my birthday
但吉布森太贵了
but you know, Gibsons are really expensive
所以我要一把便宜点的...
so I'm getting a little cheaper...
不好意思
Excuse me.
我能帮你什么忙吗
Can I help you?
我现在得回家
I need to come home now.
这是我妈和我爸的房子
This is mommy and daddy's house.
他们死了
They're dead.
天呐 我很遗憾
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
我对你爸妈的事深表遗憾
I'm really sorry about what happened with your parents.
但你不再住这里了
But yo...you don't live here anymore.
好吗 你该离开了
Okay? It...it's time for you to leave.
他们不准我弹得很响
They won't let me play it loud.
我得弹得很响
I need to play it loud.
你现在得离开了
You need to leave, now.
- 爸  - 杰希
Dad. - Jess..
杰希
Jesse.
你再不走我就报警了
You need to leave before I call the police.
好吧 够了 我要报警了
Alright, that's it, I'm calling the police.
我现在就报警了
I'm callin' 'em right now.
你太刻薄了
You were mean.
你说 以己所欲 待之于人
You say, "treat everyone like the way you want to be treated."
而你却没做到
You didn't do that.
怎么了
What?
那个可怜的家伙 显然有些不对劲
Well, the poor guy, obviously has something wrong with him
他爸妈是在我们的房子里死去的
and his parents did just die in our house.
与大卫·吉迪恩神父每日一思
对邪恶本性的深思
我们有了这样的情况
We've come to the place
用尖角 尾巴 等等
where we joke about the idea of the devil.
来开恶魔的玩笑
With the horns, and the tail, and all that.
但这是撒旦的谎言
But that is Satan's lie
用来让我们分不清真正的他
to distract us from the reality of who He is.
他不是万圣节面具
He is no mask in a Halloween store.
他不是你在电影里看到的样子
He's not what you see in the movies.
他是积极粗暴反神的个人实体
He is an active, violent anti-God personal reality.
尽管我们拒绝承认 但他就活在我们之中
And as much as we refuse to admit it, He lives through us.
他利用我们实行
He uses us to carry out
他的恶劣行径
His unspeakable deeds.
因为我们是他的爪牙 我们是他的人间恶魔
For we are His pawns, we are His demons on Earth
我们喂饱他的饥饿譯禇 覹愽 Emtёё
we satiate His hunger.
如果你心中有一丝贪婪
If you have the slightest bit of greed, in your heart
他就会把它变成雪崩
He will turn it into an avalanche.
他就会趁机进入你的灵魂
He will slither into your soul.
德克萨斯州水利水电部
最后通告
太好了 佐伊
That's really great Zooey
你这样可拿不到奥斯卡奖
that's not gonna win you any Academy Awards.
这不好笑 你生病就不该去
It's not funny, you're not supposed to go if you're sick
因为别人会被传染
because everyone else gets sick too.
看来我们要引起疾病爆发了
Well, it looks like we got an outbreak on our hands.
天呐 爸
Oh, my God. Dad.
我说我想要把飞行五号 他就把他的给我了
I said I wanted a flying V and he's given me his.
还有台马歇尔 爸 他还把他的马歇尔给我了
And a Marshall, dad, he's given me his Marshall..
爸
Dad.
我能收下 对吗
I can keep 'em right?
求你了 求你了
Please. Please.
不行
No.
我不能让你收下这把吉他
I can't let you keep this guitar.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
我要给你买一把吉他和一台音箱当生日礼物 别这样
I'm gettin' you a guitar and an amp for your birthday. Come on.
又不是飞行五号和马歇尔
Not a Flying V, and a Marshall.
彼列
我知道伦纳德已经拒绝了我的作品集
I know that Leonard already rejected my portfolio.
- 但我只要...  - 伦纳德不会看画师第二次 杰希
But I just need... - Leonard doesn't look at artists twice, Jesse.
我知道 但拜托了
Yes, I know, but please.
这个与众不同
This is different.
我以前从没有过灵感
I've never had a muse before.
我都不记得我画了这个
I don't remember painting this.
它就像是...
It's like it's, it's like somethin'..
流经我身体而来
It flowed through me.
我会想想办法
I'll see what I can do.
洛基
Rocky?
来这边 孩子
Here, boy.
过来 洛基
Come on, Rocky.
我去找洛基
Just gonna go get Rocky.
洛基
Rocky.
过来 孩子
Here, boy.
什么情况
What the fuck?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
嘿
Hey..
小佐
Zo..
好吧 你知道吗
Okay, you know what..
是我活该
...I deserve that.
完全是我活该
Okay, totally deserve that.
我真的很抱歉 小佐
I'm really sorry, Zo.
这才是我的第二天
It's only my second day.
我谁都不认识
I don't know anyone.
你却把我丢在这里
And you just left me here.
我在画画
I was painting.
我以为我在里面就待了五分钟
I thought that I was in there for five minutes.
然后我走了出来 太阳却已下山
And I stepped outside and the sun had gone down
我就慌了
and I panicked.
我没觉得我在里面待了那么久
I didn't think that I was in there for so long.
我完全茫然了
I just, I...I completely got lost in it.
- 下次别再这样 - 不会了
Don't do it again. - I won't.
- 发誓  - 我发誓
Swear. - I swear.
以我的命发誓
On my grave.
我以你的命发誓
I swear.
我们能和好吗 求你了
Can we please be friends again? Please?
你会让我收下吉他和音箱吗
Are you gonna let me keep the guitar and amp?
你们好 奥斯汀的朋友们 好久不见 你们准备好听重金属没
Hello Austin, it's been a while, but are you ready to get heavy?
我说 你们准备好听重金属没
I said, are you ready to get heavy?
剪刀脚开马歇尔音箱
Scissor kick off the Marshall stack.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
古往今来 在人类的各种宗教中
Throughout the ages, in all the various religions of man
有一个个体始终存在
there is one constant.
我们称之为撒旦
The personality of the being we call Satan.
在撒马利亚 他是巴尔
In Samaria, He was Baal.
在埃及是瑟特
In Egypt, Set.
在波斯是奥林
In Persia, Orin.
在中国 他是术士首领 被称为巫
In China, He was chief of the warlock, called Wu.
黑暗之神 堕落之神一直存在
There is always the dark God.The fallen God.
撒旦一直存在
There's always Satan.
是你跟她说可以收下吉他的吗
Did you tell her that she could keep the guitar
我以为你...
because, you know, I thought that you said that you..
天呐
Oh, my God.
那是...
Is that..
我不是有意的
I didn't mean to do this.
怎么回事
Okay, what's going on?
这是我们的女儿在被火烧
This, this is our daughter on fire.
她绝不能看到这个
She can never see this.
- 好啊 那就毁掉它 - 不行
Okay, well then destroy it. - I can't.
为什么
Why?
因为还没画完
Because it isn't finished yet.
画完了 只要你这么认为就行
No, it is, if you want it to be.
没有 事情没那么简单 阿斯特丽德
No. No, it's not that simple, Astrid.
这些孩子就像在我体内似的
It's like these children are inside of me.
乞求着 尖叫着要出来
Begging, screaming to be let out.
而我却不知道原因
And I don't know why.
来吧
Come on.
他希望是你
He wanted it to be you.
我不会让他得逞
I wouldn't let Him.
因为你很特别
'Cause you're a special one.
别 别 别
No. No...no...no.
别大喊大叫
You can't be loud.
他会让我做我不想做的事
He'll make me do that thing I don't wanna do
我不想对你那么做
and I don't wanna do that to you.
拜托 拜托了
Please, please...please.
请安静
Please, be quiet.
我放手后 你会大喊大叫吗
If I take my hand away, are you gonna be loud?
- 不会? - 嗯
- No? - Mm- mm.
发誓?
Cross your heart?
- 反悔就不得好死? - 嗯
And hope to die? - Mm-hmm.
- 嗯哼? - 嗯哼
- Mm- hmm? - Mm- hmm.
好的
Okay.
救命
Help!
别 别
Don't! Don't!
不要
Oh, no!
滚开
Get out!
快点 爸爸
Right now! Daddy!
门都锁了吗
Were the doors locked?
都锁了
Uh, yes, they were
不过杰希去了工作室...
but, um, Jess went out to the studio...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
这是他的错
It's his fault.
你说他以前在这里住过?
Now you mentioned that he'd lived here before you all?
嗯哼
Mm- hmm.
锁都没换过?
Still the same locks?
是的
Yeah.
那他可能有钥匙
Then there's every chance that he has a key
你们得换锁
which means you need to change them locks.
好的
Okay.
我觉得你们最好去旅馆住
And I think it's best if you folks move into a motel.
就住个几天
Even, just for a few days.
给我们些时间来验指纹
Give us some time to run the prints
我们要好好调查下这个人
and take a real good look into this guy.
我会整夜在外面驻守
I'll be stationed outside all night.
直到你们早上出来
Until you're up and out in the morning.
所以 不要担心
So don't you worry.
你不会有事的
You're gonna be alright.
睡会儿 好吗
Try and get some sleep, okay.
会让你感觉好些的
It's gonna make you feel a lot better.
他再来怎么办
What if he comes back?
所以警察小姐在外面
Well, that's why the police lady is outside.
他要是过了她呢
What if he gets past her?
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
- 天啊  - 阿斯特丽德
Oh, my gosh. - Astrid.
我很抱歉 我以为你是...
I'm so sorry. I thought that you were...
我没事 我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我准备上学了
I'm ready for school.
亲爱的
Sweetie...
不用 亲爱的 你今天不用上学
No,sweetie, you don't, you don't have to go to school today.
学校比这里安全
It's safer than here.
他再来我就揍扁他
If he comes back, I'll smash him.
我要迟到了
I'm gonna be late.
再见
Bye.
该死
Fuck.
- 嘿  - 杰希
Hey. - Jesse.
- 是我 - 我是玛拉
Yeah. - It's Mara.
我给伦纳德看了你的画
I showed Leonard your painting.
他认可了
He approves.
这...
That's uh, that's...
他想拜访你的工作室
He'd like to come by your studio.
看看你的工作
See what you're working on.
好的 没问题
Yeah, yeah. No, definitely.
真的太好了 随时都可以
That's great, any...any time.
伦纳德三点有空
Leonard's got an opening at three.
- 等下 今天? - 是啊
Wait, today? - Yes.
不行
No, I...I can't.
三点我得接我女儿
I...I have...I have to pick my daughter up at three.
我能提前到两点
I can push it back to two.
但这是我唯一能做的了
But that's all I can do.
要么接受 要么放弃 杰希
Take it or leave it Jesse.
拜托
Come on.
杰希 这东西是一种信仰的展现
What this is, Jesse, is a show of faith.
但我愿意抓住这个机会
But I'm willing to take that chance.
因为你的最新作品
Because your latest work is..
惊艳得令人不安
...wonderfully disturbing.
那该死的画差点害死我
Fuckin' painting nearly killed me.
（法语）
你说什么
I'm...I'm sorry.
大地之血
The blood of the Earth.
世界上最古老的非混合干邑
The world's oldest unblended cognac.
这就是我们所分享的
That's what we've been sharing.
当然不只是现在
Beside the moment of course.
既然你代表了彼列
Now that you're being represented by Belial.
你就该开始习惯好东西
It's time for you to start getting used to nice things.
伦纳德
Uh, Leonard
我乐意坐在这里和你喝掉
I'd love to sit here and drink this whole bottle
这一瓶 真的
with you right now, really, I would
但我得去接我女儿
but I gotta pick my daughter up.
我肯定你女儿不会介意
I'm sure your daughter won't mind
你迟到一两分钟的
if you're one or two minutes late.
我已经在挤时间了
I'm already pushing it.
几分钟在宏伟计划里算什么
What's a few minutes in the grander scheme?
实际上那就是一切里
Actually it's everything.
相信我 我现在听不进你说的
I'm not gonna get into it right now, just trust me.
我不能迟到
I can't be late.
常言道 真正有价值的
Well, as they say, "nothing of true worth
都会有所
"comes without some..
牺牲
...sacrifice."
敬牺牲
To sacrifice.
不是吧
Oh, no.
启动啊
Come on!
拜托
Come on.
佐伊
Zooey!
他是对的
He's right.
你是他们之中最甜蜜的糖果
You are the sweetest candy of them all.
我现在不得不做我不想做的事
I have to do that thing I don't wanna do now.
别这样
Please.
让我走 求你了
Let me go, please!
求你了
Please!
译{}者{}:{}微{}博{}@{}E{}m{}t{}e{}e
你以我的命发过誓
You swore on my grave.
听着 我知道现在这么说不是时候
Look, um, I know it doesn't seem like it right now
但...她其实很幸运
but... she's actually very lucky.
他12岁时 对一个9岁的女孩
When he was twelve, he did the same thing
做过同样的事
to a nine-year-old girl.
用石头砸了她的头
Hit her over the head with a rock
然后试图把她埋了
and then he tried to bury her.
案子交给了少年法庭 他最终
Case went to juvenile court and he ended up
在州精神病院待了20年
in state psychiatric for 20 years.
报告里有说他为什么那么做吗
Does it say in there why he did it?
我不得不用孩子喂他
"I have to feed Him children.
因为孩子是他的糖果
Because children are His candy."
他接着阐明他是指谁
He goes on to clarify who "He" is
就是撒旦本尊
none other than Satan himself.
谢谢你的耐心
Thanks for your patience.
她怎么样了
How's she doin'?
我跟杰希说过了
Like I was tellin' Jesse here.
我觉得最好的做法
I think the best course of action
就是把你们放入证人保护
is to put you into witness protection.
证人保护持续多久
And how long does witness protection last?
持续到找到他为止
As long as it takes to find him.
就汽油?
Just the gas?
要帮一把吗
Need a hand with that?
不用 我能行
Nope. I got it.
- 你确定? - 确定
You sure? - Yep.
行了
Okay.
好了
Alright.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你的钥匙 警官  - 谢谢
Your key, officer. - Thank you.
我真的很心疼那小女孩
I really feel bad for that little girl.
是啊
Yeah.
她要花很长时间才能睡着
It's gonna be a long time before she sleeps through the night.
他人呢 刚才还在这里
Now, where is he? He was just here.
爸
Dad?
不要 不要
No! No.
小佐
Zo.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
佐伊 佐伊
Zooey! Zooey!
他就在门外
He's right outside of our door!
快跑
Run!
佐伊 快
Zooey, come on!
不要 不要 不要 不要
No. No. No. No.
不要
No!
妈妈 爸爸
Mom! Daddy!
不要 不要 不要
No! No! No!
不要
No!
杰希
Jesse.
Jess..
不要
No.
佐伊 佐伊
Zooey, Zooey.
求你 别伤害她
Please, don't hurt her.
请不要伤害她 求你了
Please don't hurt her, please.
住手
No, stop!
佐伊 不要
Zooey, don't.
嘘 嘘 佐伊
Shh! Shh! Zooey.
- 不要 不要 - 不要 不要 不要
No! No! - No, no. No!
不要
No!
妈妈
Mom!
不要 不要 不要
No, no! No!
别这样 别这样 别这样
Please, please, please.
别这样
Please.
杰希
Jesse.
杰希 你快醒醒 他抓了她
Jesse, you have to wake up, he's got her.
杰希
Jesse.
她在哪
Where is she?
不要 不要
No! No!
不要 不要 不要 不要
No! No, no, no!
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no!
嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh! Shh!
看 看 看
Look, look, look!
看啊
Look.
是他
It's Him.
坚持住 佐伊
Hang on, Zooey!
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no!
爸爸
Daddy!
Ah, daddy!
不要 不要
No, no.
小佐 佐伊
Zo.. Zooey..
佐伊 你得到我这来
Zooey, you need to come to me.
快速跳过来就好了
Just jump really fast.
我办不到
I can't!
请相信我
Please trust me.
我会接住你的 小佐
I'm gonna catch you, Zo.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
佐伊
Zooey.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我能感觉到他们在我体内
I can feel them inside me
乞求着 尖叫着
begging, screaming
要出来
to be let out.
而我却不知道原因
And I don't know why.
恶魔的糖果
译者：微博@Emtee